export const Questions = [
    
    {
        prompt: "1) Which of the following is the correct name of React.js?",
        optionA: "a. React",
        optionB: "b. Reactjs",
        optionC: "c. ReactJS",
        optionD: "d. All of the above",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2) Which of the following are the advantages of React.js?",
        optionA: "a. Increase the application's performance with Virtual DOM.",
        optionB: "b. Easy to integrate with other frameworks since it is a library.",
        optionC: "c. Can render both on client and server side.",
        optionD: "d. All of the above",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3) Which of the following is not a disadvantage of React.js?",
        optionA: "a. React.js has only a view layer. ",
        optionB: "b. The library of React.js is pretty large.",
        optionC: "c. The JSX in React.js makes code easy to read and write.",
        optionD: "d. The learning curve can be steep in React.js.",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4) Which command is used to install create-react-app?",
        optionA: "a. npm install -g create-react-app",
        optionB: "b. npm install create-react-app",
        optionC: "c. npm install -f create-react-app",
        optionD: "d. install -g create-react-app",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5) What of the following is used to increase performance?",
        optionA: "a. Original DOM",
        optionB: "b. Virtual DOM",
        optionC: "c. Both A and B.",
        optionD: "d. None of the above",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6) Which acts as an input of a class-based component?",
        optionA: "a. Class",
        optionB: "b. Factory",
        optionC: "c. Render",
        optionD: "d. Props",
        answer: "D",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7) Which of the following is used to create a class inheritance?",
        optionA: "a. Create",
        optionB: "b. Inherits",
        optionC: "c. Extends",
        optionD: "d. All of the above",
        answer: "C",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8) Which is used to pass data to a component from outside?",
        optionA: "a. props",
        optionB: "b. render with arguments",
        optionC: "c. setState",
        optionD: "d. PropTypes",
        answer: "A",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9) Which of the following is not a part of ReactDOM?",
        optionA: "a. ReactDOM.hydrate()",
        optionB: "b. ReactDOM.destroy()",
        optionC: "c. ReactDOM.createPortal()",
        optionD: "d. All of the mentioned",
        answer: "B",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10) Which of the following is correct about prop in react?",
        optionA: "a. Can be changed inside another component",
        optionB: "b. Can be changed inside the component",
        optionC: "c. Cannot be changed in the component",
        optionD: "d. All of the above",
        answer: "D",
    },
    
];
    